tradetracker.net 2014-12-30

# TradeTracker privacy statement - TradeTracker UK

At TradeTracker, your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we have provided this statement explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed. To make this statement easy to find, we have made it available on our homepage and at every location where personally identifiable information may be requested.

### Information we collect

TradeTracker collects many kinds of information in order to operate effectively and provide you the best products, services and experiences we can. We collect information when you register, sign in and use our sites and services. We also may get information from other companies. We collect this information in a variety of ways, including from web forms, technologies like [cookies](https://www.tradetracker.com/gb/privacy/cookie), web logging and software on your computer or other device.

### How we use your personal information

TradeTracker uses the information we collect to operate, improve and personalize the products and services we offer. We also may use the information to communicate with you, for example, informing you about your account and security updates. And we may use the information to help make the ads you see on our ad-supported services more relevant.

### Reasons we share your personal information

Except as described in this privacy statement, we won't disclose your personal information to a third party without your consent.

### Accessing your personal information

Some TradeTracker services give you the ability to view or edit your personal information online. To help prevent others from viewing your personal information, you first will be required to sign in. How you can access your personal information will depend on which sites or services you have used.

### Communication preferences

You can stop the delivery of future promotional email from TradeTracker sites and services by following the specific instructions in the email you receive. Depending on the respective service, you may also have the option of proactively making choices about the receipt of promotional email, telephone calls, and postal mail for particular TradeTracker sites or services.

### TradeTracker account

A TradeTracker account allows you to sign into TradeTracker products, websites and services. When you create a TradeTracker account, we ask you to provide certain information. When you sign into a website or service using your TradeTracker account, we collect certain information in order to verify your identity on behalf of the website or service, to protect you from malicious account usage, and to protect the efficiency and security of the TradeTracker account service. We also send certain, non-personal information to a website or service you have signed into with your TradeTracker account.
